https://www.eggart.com.au/privacy.php?osCsid=lq11s7tquvd4ngkg5m9vd1cc62

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Top » Catalogue » Privacy Policy
A&J Crafts Pty Ltd Privacy Policy
Introduction
A&J Crafts Pty Ltd regards customer privacy as an important part of our relationship with our customers. The following privacy policy applies to all A&J Crafts Pty Ltd users, and conforms to
Internet privacy standards.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact A&J Crafts Pty Ltd by phone at (07) 3374 4811, or internationally at
IAC + 61 + 7 + 3374 4811, or by email at info@eggart.com.au
Collection of Information
For you to use the A&J Crafts Pty Ltd website, we may require information from you so that we can provide the best service possible.
All correspondence, particularly with regard to sales, support, and accounts, may be collected and stored.
Any information collected by A&J Crafts Pty Ltd is collected via correspondence from you or your company. This may be via the telephone, email, mail, fax or directly through our website.
Use of Collection Information
Any details collected from A&J Crafts Pty Ltd customers are required to provide you with our products and/or services, and a high level of customer service.
Correspondence is recorded to provide service references, and to assist in our staff development.
Storage of Collected Information
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our website, we encrypt that information using secure
socket layer technology (SSL). When Credit Card details are collected, we simply pass them on to be processed as required. We never permanently store complete Credit Card details.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.
If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at info@eggart.com.au
Access to Collected Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing us
at info@eggart.com.au
Orders
If you purchase a product or service from us, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. You may be required to provide contact information (such as name, email,
and postal address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).
We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
Communications
A&J Crafts Pty Ltd uses personally identifiable information for essential communications, such as emails, accounts information, and critical service details. We may also use this
information for other purposes, including some promotional emails. If at any time a customer wishes not to receive such correspondence, they can request to be removed from any
mailing lists by emailing us at info@eggart.com.au
Third Parties
A&J Crafts Pty Ltd may at its discretion use other third parties to provide essential services on our site or for our business processes. We may share your details as necessary for the
third party to provide that service.
These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.
A&J Crafts Pty Ltd does not share any information with third parties for any unknown or unrelated uses.
Legal
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply
with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.
Links
Links on the A&J Crafts Pty Ltd site to external entities are not covered within this policy. The terms and conditions set out in this privacy statement only cover the domain name of eggart.com.au
Changes to Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what
information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it
frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by Email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
Continue
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Categories *Specials*BasesBeads and PearlsBell HandlesBooks & DVDsBraidsBrass RodsBrooch FindingsCameosCatalogueCeramicsClocksDecalsDiamond SawsEgg KitsEgg ShellsEgg-in-WrapFigurines->FindingsGlues and FinishesHingesLegsMirrorsMiscellaneousMusic Boxes & AccessoriesPaintsPinsPorcelain Half DollsPre-Cut EggsRhinestonesSilk PrintsSonie Ames PrintsStandsTasselsTeapot Handles & SpoutsTools
Information
Shipping & Returns Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Copyright © 2020 Egg Art Australia
7 Willowbrook St, Kenmore Hills, Qld, 4069, Australia
Email Us: info@eggart.com.au
Phone: (07) 3374 4811
Int Phone: IAC + 61 + 7 + 3374 4811
